<resources>
    <string name="app_name">AMIMATCH</string>
    <string name="placeholder_name">Placeholder Name</string>
    <string name="placeholder_age">XX years old</string>
    <string name="placeholder_gender">Gender</string>
    <string name="placeholder_hobbies">Hobbies</string>
    <string name="placeholder_interests">Interests</string>
    <string name="placeholder_bio">Bio</string>
    <string name="profile_picture">Profile Picture</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <!-- Firebase database fields -->
    <string name="dbfemale">female</string>
    <string name="dbmale">male</string>
    <string name="title_activity_check_profile_before_matched">activity_checkProfileBeforeMatched
    </string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="match_notification">Match Notification</string>
    <string name="ok">ok</string>
    <string name="permission_camera_rationale">Request for camera permission</string>
    <string name="permission_contacts_rationale">GALLERY PERMISSION</string>
    <string name="permision_available_camera">camera available</string>
    <string name="privacy_policy_content">
    <![CDATA[
    <b>Privacy Policy AMI-MATCH 2024</b><br><br>
    This Privacy Policy explains how your personal information is collected, used, and disclosed by the AmiMatch ("the App")
    Developed by <a href="https://www.instagram.com/adityaupreti__/">Aditya Upreti</a> ("the Developer").<br><br>
    <b>Contact Us</b><br><br>
    If you have any questions or suggestions about this App, please contact us at <a href="mailto:aupreti73@gmail.com">aupreti73@gmail.com</a>.
    You can also follow me on <a href="https://www.instagram.com/adityaupreti__/">Instagram</a> for updates and news.<br><br>
    <b>Testing Phase and Affiliation</b><br><br>
    The App is intended for university use as part of a mini project and is still in the testing phase. It may have bugs, crashes, and instability. The App is not affiliated with the university.<br><br>
    <b>Information Collection and Use</b><br><br>
    The App collects certain personal information provided by you during the registration process, including your name, email address, age, gender, and profile image. This information is stored securely on Google\'s Firestore database.<br><br>
    <b>Access to Data</b><br><br>
    The Developer has access to all data stored on the Firestore database, including your registration information, age, gender, and profile image. This data can be modified, deleted, or accessed by the Developer for troubleshooting purposes.<br><br>
    <b>User Interactions</b><br><br>
    The application acknowledges its role in facilitating interactions between users; however, it does not endorse or guarantee the outcome of these interactions. Users are strongly advised to exercise caution and discretion when engaging in communication with others.<br><br>
    <b>Sharing of Information</b><br><br>
    Protecting your privacy is our priority. We want to assure you that AMI-MATCH does not share or collect your personal information for any purpose other than what is explicitly outlined in this Privacy Policy.<br><br>
    <b>Prohibited Activities</b><br><br>
    To maintain a positive and safe environment within the App, certain activities are strictly prohibited. These include but are not limited to creating fake profiles or images, misusing the App, engaging in abusive behavior towards others, displaying inappropriate conduct, or impersonating someone else. Any accounts found involved in such activities may face immediate disablement or deletion, depending on the severity of the situation.<br><br>
    <b>Changes to This Privacy Policy</b><br><br>
    The Developer may update this Privacy Policy from time to time. You are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. By continuing to use the App after any modifications to this Privacy Policy, you acknowledge and agree to the updated terms.<br><br>
    ]]>
</string>


</resources>